

<Moisés Gonçalves_>

<Junior_FullStack_Developer>

ABOUT ME!

As a chess player, I have developed problem-solving skills and logical thinking this aligned to my eagerness to reshift my career and some insights from my developer brother took me to take a leap of faith and enroll on <Academia de Código_>'s 14 week intensive bootcamp.

I have professional experience in construction work and as a waiter. My time in construction taught me the importance of organization and planning. As a waiter, I honed my communication and customer service abilities. These experiences have given me a strong foundation in teamwork, adaptability, and interpersonal skills.

EXPERIENCE

WAITER

Pastelaria South Africa

2017 - 2020

WAITER

Café Meia Noite

2014 - 216

CONSTRUCTION WORKER

Escala Padrão

2007 - 2013

CONTACTS



+351 916 762 102



moisesgoncalves1986@gmail.com



Braga/Portugal



https://www.linkedin.com/in/moises-goncalves-dev/



http://github.com/moisesgoncalves86

EDUCATION

<Academia de Código_>

Junior FullStack Developer

Jan 2023 - Apr 2023

Qualidade de Basto

High School Diploma

Nov 2002 - Dec 2005

SKILLS

- Java
- JavaScript
- HTML
- SQL
- Git
- Maven
- jQuery
- Spring Framework
- Tomcat
- Bootstrap
- CSS
- MVC
- Rest APIs
- JUnit
- OOP

HOBBIES

- Cycling
- F1
- Chess

LANGUAGES

- Portuguese
- English
- Spanish
- French